Ted Koppel Collection
Ted Koppel Collection
- Nightline, 1980-2005
  - 1997
    - Nightline: Janet Reno and The Independent Counsel Statute, 04/14/1997; koppel_nl97041401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White: Race and The Thin Blue Line, 04/15/1997; koppel_nl97041501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Building Brains, 04/16/1997; koppel_nl97041601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Are the Tobacco Companies Caving In?: Major Tobacco Firms Consider Settling Suits, 04/17/1997; koppel_nl97041701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Hajj: The Pilgrimage to Mecca Made by Muslims, 04/18/1997; koppel_nl97041801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Digital: Coming Soon to a TV Near You, 04/21/1997; koppel_nl97042101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Ending the Hostage Crisis in Peru, 04/22/1997; koppel_nl97042201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: What's the Oldest a Women Should Be Giving Birth?, 04/23/1997; koppel_nl97042301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Jimmy Carter and Colin Powell Want You: A Call to Community Service, 04/24/1997; koppel_nl97042401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Enter The Dragon: Revisiting Hong Kong Prior to Turnover to China, 04/25/1997; koppel_nl97042501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Enter The Dragon: When The Chinese Take Over Hong Kong?, 04/28/1997; koppel_nl97042801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Will Hong Kong Have A Tiananmen?: Interview With Hong Kong Executive-Designate, 04/29/1997; koppel_nl97042901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Politics American-Style, With a British Twist, 04/30/1997; koppel_nl97043001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The United States v. Timothy James McVeigh, 05/01/1997; koppel_nl97050101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Nightmare in Paradise: Claims of False Arrest, Extortion on St. Vincent, 05/02/1997; koppel_nl97050201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Latest Battle in The Tobacco Wars: RJ Reynolds Found Not Liable in Cancer Death, 05/05/1997; koppel_nl97050501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Illegal Drugs, Mexico and NAFTA: Rise in Illegal Drugs Entering US from Mexico, 05/06/1997; koppel_nl97050601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Web Hubbell and What the Clintons Knew and When, 05/07/1997; koppel_nl97050701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Growing Nowhere Fast: Placid Suburbs Develop the Problems of Cities, 05/08/1997; koppel_nl97050801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Great Kate: Praise For Katharine Hepburn's Achievements, 05/09/1997; koppel_nl97050901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The US and Russia: US Money Aids Russia's Crumbling Space Program, 05/12/1997; koppel_nl97051201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Fool's Gold: Investors Lose Big in Bre-X Scam, 05/13/1997; koppel_nl97051301; tape mislabeled: episode not on tape
    - Nightline: A Respected Physician: Austrian Doctor Supervised Murder of Children, 05/14/1997; koppel_nl97051401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The West versus Washington: Clash Over Land Preservation in Utah, 05/15/1997; koppel_nl97051501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Flirting with Disaster: The Dilemma of Looking for Life in Space, 05/16/1997; koppel_nl97051601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Going Pro: African-Americans Leave College to Play Pro Ball, 05/19/1997; koppel_nl97051901; tape mislabeled: episode not on tape
    - Nightline: The Holes in the Oklahoma City Bombing Case, 05/20/1997; koppel_nl97052001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: American Business and Chinese Prison Labor Camps, 05/21/1997; koppel_nl97052101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Reasonable Doubt: Defending Timothy McVeigh, 05/22/1997; koppel_nl97052201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Reclaiming Yosemite: Forces of Nature Restore Yosemite's Luster, 05/23/1997; koppel_nl97052301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Hollywood in Tehran: Iran Through the Filmmaker's Lens, 05/26/1997; koppel_nl97052601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: William Jefferson Clinton v. Paula Corbin Jones, 05/27/1997; koppel_nl97052701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Liability of the Tobacco Lawyers: What are the Legal and Ethical Limits for Lawyers?, 05/28/1997; koppel_nl97052801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Case Against Timothy McVeigh, 05/29/1997; koppel_nl97052901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Case Not Closed: JonBenet Ramsey Murder Remains Still Unsolved, 05/30/1997; koppel_nl97053001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Verdict in the Oklahoma City Bombing Trial, 06/02/1997; koppel_nl97060201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: When Will US Troops Leave Bosnia?, 06/03/1997; koppel_nl97060301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Conversation with Bob Bennett, 06/04/1997; koppel_nl97060401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Drawing the Line: Sex, Adultery and The Military, 06/05/1997; koppel_nl97060501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: John Plummer's Burden: American GI Apologizes to Vietnamese Woman, 06/06/1997; koppel_nl97060601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Adultery, Good Order and Military Justice: Gen. Ralston, Kelly Flinn and Sex in the Military, 06/09/1997; koppel_nl97060901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Timothy McVeigh: Choosing Life or Death, 06/10/1997; koppel_nl97061001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Noel's Wish: An Intimate Portrait, 06/11/1997; koppel_nl97061101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Rupert Murdoch: Examination of a Media Mogul, 06/12/1997; koppel_nl97061201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Timothy McVeigh, The Day Of Reckoning: The Oklahoma City Bombing Verdict, 06/13/1997; koppel_nl97061301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Project Grads: A Program for Teen Mothers and Their Children, 06/16/1997; koppel_nl97061601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Gang Busting: Is an Effective Tactic Violating the Law?, 06/17/1997; koppel_nl97061701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Apologizing for Slavery: Should Congress Issue Formal Apology for Slavery, 06/18/1997; koppel_nl97061801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Deal That's Good for Big Tobacco: Can It Be Good for The Nation?, 06/19/1997; koppel_nl97061901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Frogs: What Are They Really Telling Us?, 06/20/1997; koppel_nl97062001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Fight Over Religion in Our Schools: Public Financing of Education in Religious Schools, 06/23/1997; koppel_nl97062301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The WNBA and the Changing Role of Women's Sports, 06/24/1997; koppel_nl97062401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Old Man and The Sea: Remembering Jacques Cousteau, 06/25/1997; koppel_nl97062501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Case of Harold Nicholson: CIA Officer Nicholson Sells Secrets to Russia, 06/26/1997; koppel_nl97062601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Nation's Lawyer: Behind Scenes of a Supreme Court Term, 06/27/1997; koppel_nl97062701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Enter The Dragon: A Day in Life of New Hong Kong, 06/30/1997; koppel_nl97063001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Has Mike Tyson Finally Gone Too Far?: The Mike Tyson Biting Evander Holyfield Incident, 07/01/1997; koppel_nl97070101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Wonderful Life: Remembering Jimmy Stewart, 07/02/1997; koppel_nl97070201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Roswell: The Making of a Myth, 07/03/1997; koppel_nl97070301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Family Business: Brothers Attempt to Keep Family Company Operating, 07/04/1997; koppel_nl97070401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Mars Rising: Pathfinder Transmits Views of The Red Planet, 07/07/1997; koppel_nl97070701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Sexual Misconduct in the Army: A Talk with Retired Sergeant Major Brenda Hoster, 07/08/1997; koppel_nl97070801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Will Tyson Fight Again?, 07/09/1997; koppel_nl97070901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Hearings Into Campaign Reform: Is Anyone Watching?, 07/10/1997; koppel_nl97071001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Stadol: User Beware, 07/11/1997; koppel_nl97071101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Innocence and the Death Penalty, 07/14/1997; koppel_nl97071401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Bizarre Murder of Gianni Versace, 07/15/1997; koppel_nl97071501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: What It Takes to Catch a Serial Killer, 07/16/1997; koppel_nl97071601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Another Close Call for Mir, 07/17/1997; koppel_nl97071701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The LBJ Tapes: What August 4, 1964 was Like for President Johnson, 07/18/1997; koppel_nl97071801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The LBJ Tapes: Newly Released Tapes Recorded In Summer, 1964, 07/21/1997; koppel_nl97072101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Unlocking the Mysteries of the Brain: Emotionally Scarred Adopted from Eastern Europe, 07/22/1997; koppel_nl97072201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Latest on the Andrew Cunanan Case, 07/23/1997; koppel_nl97072301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Two Different and Extraordinary Views of Cunanan, 07/24/1997; koppel_nl97072401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: To Be the First Battling for The Cure, 07/25/1997; koppel_nl97072501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Trial of Pol Pot, 07/28/1997; koppel_nl97072801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Trial of Pol Pot, 07/29/1997; koppel_nl97072901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Breaking News from Two Troubled Regions: The Middle East and Southeast Asia, 07/30/1997; koppel_nl97073001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Campaign Finance Hearings, 07/31/1997; koppel_nl97073101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Betrayal: Sexual Abuse and the Catholic Clergy, 08/01/1997; koppel_nl97080101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Courts in Crisis: Where Have All the Judges Gone?, 08/04/1997; koppel_nl97080401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Putting The FBI Under A Public Microscope, 08/05/1997; koppel_nl97080501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Papers Tobacco Industry Didn't Want You to See, 08/06/1997; koppel_nl97080601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Breaking the Taboo to Combat AIDS In Uganda, 08/07/1997; koppel_nl97080701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: www.hoax!.com: False Stories or Hoaxes Spread Over the Internet, 08/08/1997; koppel_nl97080801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Nightmare in Paradise: St. Vincent Dismisses US Couple's Murder Charge, 08/11/1997; koppel_nl97081101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Part-Time Work: Are We All Headed in That Direction?, 08/12/1997; koppel_nl97081201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Dilemma of Capturing Bosnia's War Criminals, 08/13/1997; koppel_nl97081301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Day in the Life of Marion Barry, 08/14/1997; koppel_nl97081401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The King: Elvis 20 Years After His Death, 08/15/1997; koppel_nl97081501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Agreement Between UPS and the Teamsters, 08/18/1997; koppel_nl97081801
    - Nightline: VMI: The Women Have Arrived, 08/19/1997; koppel_nl97081901
    - Nightline: Covenant Marriages: New Louisiana Law Makes it Harder to Divorce, 08/20/1997; koppel_nl97082001
    - Nightline: The Blue Wall, Part 1: Voices from The NYPD's Brooklyn Precincts, 08/21/1997; koppel_nl97082101
    - Nightline: The Blue Wall, Part 2: Police Brutality and Police Silence, 08/22/1997; koppel_nl97082201
    - Nightline: Is Enough Being Done to Keep Your Food Safe?, 08/25/1997; koppel_nl97082501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White, Part 1: Race and the Criminal Justice System, 08/26/1997; koppel_nl97082601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White, Part 2: Is The Criminal Justice System Fair?, 08/27/1997; koppel_nl97082701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Affirmative Action: Is California Setting a Trend for the Nation?, 08/28/1997; koppel_nl97082801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Montserrat: Gem of the Caribbean Now a Ghost Town, 08/29/1997; koppel_nl97082901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Pursuing Diana: How Much Is One Picture Worth?, 09/01/1997; koppel_nl97090101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Diary of a Princess: Diana in Her Own Words, 09/02/1997; koppel_nl97090201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Art of the Deal: Tracking Down the Gardner Masterpieces, 09/03/1997; koppel_nl97090301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: From Welfare to Work: Wisconsin's Answer, 09/04/1997; koppel_nl97090401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Farewell to a Princess, 09/05/1997; koppel_nl97090501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Burning Man Festival, 09/08/1997; koppel_nl97090801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Corner: Street Corner Life's Effect on Inner City Youth, 09/09/1997; koppel_nl97090901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Al Gore on the Hot Seat: Effect of Fund-Raising in White House on Al Gore, 09/10/1997; koppel_nl97091001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Pressure on US to Support Total Land Mine Ban, 09/11/1997; koppel_nl97091101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Mother Teresa: A Mission of Mercy, 09/12/1997; koppel_nl97091201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 1: The Dawning of the Digital Age, 09/15/1997; koppel_nl97091501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Secret Shame: Social Engineering of Sweden's Past, 09/16/1997; koppel_nl97091601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Surviving The Unabomber, 09/17/1997; koppel_nl97091701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White: Legacy of Little Rock, 09/18/1997; koppel_nl97091801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: America in Black and White: Scars of Little Rock, 09/19/1997; koppel_nl97091901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 2: When Seeing is No Longer Believing, 09/22/1997; koppel_nl97092201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Man Without a Face: A Conversation with Markus Wolf, 09/23/1997; koppel_nl97092301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Week in the Life of a Volcano: Volcano's Effect on Montserrat and Inhabitants, 09/24/1997; koppel_nl97092401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Winnie Mandela: Reaching for Power, Falling from Grace, 09/25/1997; koppel_nl97092501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Photographers Shoot Back: Those Behind the Cameras Take Their Best Shots, 09/26/1997; koppel_nl97092601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 3: Technology Reshaping the Way We Learn, 09/29/1997; koppel_nl97092901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Deformed Frogs: One Step Closer to Solving the Mystery, 09/30/1997; koppel_nl97093001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Christian Coalition: Is It Choosing Sides?, 10/01/1997; koppel_nl97100101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: School Busing: Has the Payoff Been Worth the Pain?, 10/02/1997; koppel_nl97100201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Promise Keepers: Answering the Call, 10/03/1997; koppel_nl97100301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 4: The Bilbao Guggenheim Museum, 10/06/1997; koppel_nl97100601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Campaign Fund-Raising and the Tale of the Tapes, 10/07/1997; koppel_nl97100701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Lady Bird Johnson Diaries: November 22, 1963, 10/08/1997; koppel_nl97100801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Lady Bird Johnson Diaries: The Aftermath of the Kennedy Assassination, 10/09/1997; koppel_nl97100901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Eric Davis Beating Cancer, 10/10/1997; koppel_nl97101001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 5: Revolution in Silicon Valley, 10/13/1997; koppel_nl97101301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: White House Tapes, The Politicians, The Public: President Clinton's Approval Rating Remains High, 10/14/1997; koppel_nl97101401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: El Nino: Are We Scaring Ourselves to Death?, 10/15/1997; koppel_nl97101501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: A Conversation with Jane Alexander, 10/16/1997; koppel_nl97101601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Rating Game: Rating TV Programs for Content, 10/17/1997; koppel_nl97101701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 6: How the Revolution is Being Shaped by Microsoft, 10/20/1997; koppel_nl97102001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Child Care and Working Parents, 10/21/1997; koppel_nl97102101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Media and New Medical Treatments, 10/22/1997; koppel_nl97102201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Eyewitnesses to a Famine, 10/23/1997; koppel_nl97102301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Whatever Happened to The World Series?, 10/24/1997; koppel_nl97102401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Meaning of the Plunge on Wall Street, 10/27/1997; koppel_nl97102701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: An Idiot's Guide to the Stock Market, 10/28/1997; koppel_nl97102801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The US-China Summit, 10/29/1997; koppel_nl97102901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Truth and Consequences: The Chinese Leader's Lesson in Freedom of Speech, 10/30/1997; koppel_nl97103001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Sex, Drugs and HIV: Chautauqua County Faces Reality About HIV Threat, 10/31/1997; koppel_nl97103101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 7: Whatever Happened To HDTV?, 11/03/1997; koppel_nl97110301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Trial of Terry Nichols/Election Day Results, 11/04/1997; koppel_nl97110401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The World According to George Soros, 11/05/1997; koppel_nl97110501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: What Can the US Do About Saddam Hussein?: Saddam Still Stockpiles Mass Destruction Weapons, 11/06/1997; koppel_nl97110601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: How Safe is Your Money Invested in a Mutual Fund?, 11/07/1997; koppel_nl97110701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Was the Au Pair's Judge's Decision Fair?, 11/10/1997; koppel_nl97111001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Multiple Births, 11/11/1997; koppel_nl97111101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: How Far is Iraq Prepared to Go?: An Interview with Iraq's Deputy Prime Minister, 11/12/1997; koppel_nl97111201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Great Game: Jockeying for the World's Last Oil Bonanza, 11/13/1997; koppel_nl97111301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Readings from the Nixon Tapes, 11/14/1997; koppel_nl97111401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 8: The Role of Computers, 11/17/1997; koppel_nl97111701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Readings from the Nixon Tapes, 11/18/1997; koppel_nl97111801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The McCaughey Septuplets, 11/19/1997; koppel_nl97111901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: An Interview with Winnie Mandela, 11/20/1997; koppel_nl97112001; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Black Teacher-White Teacher: The Sharon Taxman Case, 11/21/1997; koppel_nl97112101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 9: Technology's Haves and Have-Nots, 11/24/1997; koppel_nl97112401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Accusations Against Winnie Mandela, 11/25/1997; koppel_nl97112501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Singing for Their Souls, Part 1, 11/26/1997; koppel_nl97112601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Singing for Their Souls, Part 2, 11/27/1997; koppel_nl97112701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Eddie: The Story of A Lifetime, 11/28/1997; koppel_nl97112801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 10: A Day in the Life of Microsoft, 12/01/1997; koppel_nl97120101; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Terror on the Nile: Anatomy of a Massacre, Part 1, 12/02/1997; koppel_nl97120201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Terror on The Nile: Anatomy of a Massacre, Part 2, 12/03/1997; koppel_nl97120301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: On Sacred Ground: Controversial Burials at Arlington Cemetery, 12/04/1997; koppel_nl97120401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: On Sacred Ground: The Way Washington Works, 12/05/1997; koppel_nl97120501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 11: Cyber Terror, 12/08/1997; koppel_nl97120801
    - Nightline: The Ad Campaign and the Kyoto Summit, 12/09/1997; koppel_nl97120901
    - Nightline: American Gothic: What's Behind the Obsession with the Dark Side?, 12/10/1997; koppel_nl97121001
    - Nightline: The Good Nazi: the Nazi Who Saved Thousands of Chinese Lives, 12/11/1997; koppel_nl97121101
    - Nightline: Drawing Laughter: The Cartoonists of The New Yorker, 12/12/1997; koppel_nl97121201
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 12: Women and the Revolution in a Box, 12/15/1997; koppel_nl97121501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Oklahoma City Revisited: The Trial of Terry Nichols, 12/16/1997; koppel_nl97121601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Steven Spielberg and Amistad: Who Owns History?, 12/17/1997; koppel_nl97121701; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Keepers, Part 1: Terrorist Bombing Inspires Love and Kindness, 12/18/1997; koppel_nl97121801; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Keepers, Part 2: Lockerbie, Scotland: Keepers of Memory and Love, 12/19/1997; koppel_nl97121901; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Revolution in a Box, Part 13: The Future of Man vs. Machine, 12/22/1997; koppel_nl97122201; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Nichols Verdict, 12/23/1997; koppel_nl97122301; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Gift of Music: The Boys Choir of Harlem, 12/24/1997; koppel_nl97122401; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: The Gift of Music: The Boys Choir of Harlem, 12/25/1997; koppel_nl97122501; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)
    - Nightline: Is Fat Good?, 12/26/1997; koppel_nl97122601; Videotape, VHS, dub (Box 157)